carsmarters.com 2011-01-20

# Privacy | Road Tests, Auto Features

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Carreviewgate.com's websites. Personally Identifiable Information may be: Name, Address, Email address and/or Phone number. 

Users may submit Personally Identifiable Information to us, but we do not share any Personally Identifiable Information with any outside parties. By submiting reviews, the user agrees that the content becomes property of Carreviewgate.com, and Carreviewgate.com reserves the rights to edit, analyze, use and/or display all content that users provide to us, with reasonable effort to protect user's Personally Identifiable Information. 

Carreviewgate.com will identify the user's name and/or email address on Carreviewgate.com's sites only with user's consent. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women, but we do not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [ here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

Carreviewgate.com is not responsibly for any information submited or collected on sites managed and operated by Carreviewgate.com's partners or advertisers. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
